{
    "subject": "resource/Olainfarm",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "resource/Pharmaceutical_drug",
    "human_readable": "Olainfarm is in the industry of Pharmaceutical drug.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.878948986530304,
            "question": "What industry does Olainfarm operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7717549204826355,
            "question": "Is Olainfarm involved in the healthcare sector?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7463053464889526,
            "question": "Does Olainfarm develop new medicines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.679058313369751,
            "question": "What kind of products does Olainfarm manufacture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5589649081230164,
            "question": "What is the primary function of Olainfarm's products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295085310935974,
            "question": "Is Olainfarm a global company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45309263467788696,
            "question": "Are there any specific diseases that Olainfarm focuses on treating?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44285205006599426,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a product made by Olainfarm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3456383943557739,
            "question": "Does Olainfarm conduct research and development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21594209969043732,
            "question": "What is the main purpose of pharmaceutical drugs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olainfarm is in the industry of Pharmaceutical drug.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8092_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Olainfarm conduct research and development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8092_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a product made by Olainfarm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8092_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific diseases that Olainfarm focuses on treating?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8092_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8092_52.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nMultiple documents clearly state that Olainfarm is involved in the pharmaceutical industry.  Here are some examples:\n\n* **file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8092/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt:** \"Olainfarm is one of the leading representatives of the pharmaceutical industry in the Baltic States.\"\n* **file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8092/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt:** \"Olainfarm is the leading manufacturer in the chemical and pharmaceutical sector of the Baltic States\"\n* **file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8092/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt:** \"Olainfarm is the leading manufacturer in the chemical and pharmaceutical sector of the Baltic States\" \n* **file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8092/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt:** \"Joint Stock Company Olainfarm is one of the largest companies in the Baltic countries with more than 45 years of experience in the production of pharmaceuticals, active chemical substances and other chemicals.\"\n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention Olainfarm as a company involved in the production of pharmaceuticals, active chemical substances, and other chemicals. They also mention that Olainfarm is one of the largest representatives of the pharmaceutical industry in Latvia and other Baltic countries, which indicates its primary industry is indeed Pharmaceutical drug."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Olainfarm being engaged in the production of finished pharmaceutical formulations, pharmaceuticals and food supplements, as well as chemicals and active pharmaceutical ingredients. This clearly supports that Olainfarm is indeed in the industry of Pharmaceutical drugs."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}